https://www.oxford-architects.com/legal/privacy

COVID-19 - PRACTICE STATEMENT
As Government guidance develops we are writing to advise you of the steps we are taking to maintain business continuity.
Our studios in Oxford and Bristol are now open and being managed in accordance with our Return to Office Policy.
We continue to provide our full range of Architectural, Principal Designer, Party Wall and Graphic Design services through a combination of home and office based working.
We thank all our clients, staff, fellow consultants and contractors for their ongoing support.
Best wishesCharles Webster, Chairman
Home
Projects
All
Commercial
Science & Technology
Community
Education
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how Oxford Architects uses and protects any information that you give Oxford Architects when you use this website. Oxford Architects is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Oxford Architects may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 1.11.2015. What we collectWe may collect the following information:Contact information including email addressAnonymous website analytics statisticsWhat we do with the information we gatherWe require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:Internal record keeping
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
SecurityWe are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.How we use cookiesA cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.Links to other websitesOur website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.Controlling your personal informationYou may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes.We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to Oxford Architects LLP, Bagley Croft, Hinksey Hill, Oxford OX1 5BS.If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
Terms of Use
Privacy
Cookies
Ten4 Design
Copyright © Oxford Architects LLP 2020
Oxford
01865 329 100
Bagley Croft
